Igor Lisboa

+55 21 99742 7343 | igor.rodrigues.lisboa@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/igor-lisboa-261020141 | github.com/igor-lisboa

SUMMARY

Full stack developer with 7 years of experience in the financial, real estate, and medical industries.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C#, PL/SQL, JavaScript, PHP, Java, Python, C, C++, VB, ASP.

Technologies: .NET, TypeScript, React, PostgreSQL, Rabbit MQ, Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, Azure DevOps, GIT Hub, GIT Lab, AWS, S3, SQS, Dynamo DB, Mongo DB, Redis, SQL Server, MySQL, Oracle, Vue, Laravel, Spring.

EDUCATION

Universidade Federal Fluminense (UFF)

Bachelor's degree in Information Systems

Jan 2017 - Jan 2022

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Software Engineer

Jan 2024 - current

Proanum

Developed a module (API, Worker Services, Front-End) to automatically track the real estate asset payments.

- RESULT Approximately 90% time savings in monitoring by analysts (resulting in approximately **BRL 200K/year** savings or around **2000 hours** saved).
- TECH .NET, C#, React, PostgreSQL, Rabbit MQ, Docker, CI/CD, GIT Hub, AWS, EDA (Event-driven architecture), TDD (Test-driven development).

Full Stack Developer Jul 2021 – Jan 2024

BTG Pactual Bank

Developed APIs, Worker Services, Front-Ends for trading financial assets, with flexible parameterizable rules.

- RESULT This enabled the Bank to expand its asset portfolio to include new assets with very high transaction volumes, with mandatory flexible parameterization rules. Potential AUM of more than **BRL 4 billion** per year due to the new funds in operation.
- TECH .NET, C#, React, Rabbit MQ, PostgreSQL, Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, Azure DevOps, Redis, AWS, S3, Dynamo, EDA (Event-driven architecture), TDD (Test-driven development).

Developed scalable microservice in .NET for settling financial assets.

- RESULT Reduced the average response time from **1.2 seconds to 0.45 seconds** and centralized the daily load volume in the new microservice (previously handled by multiple disparate systems).
- TECH .NET, C#, Vue, Rabbit MQ, PostgreSQL, Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, Azure DevOps, AWS, Redis, TDD (Test-driven development).

Developed automation for reports for Investment Funds (Performance, Management, Portfolio Composition, Liquidity).

- RESULT Approximately 15% time savings for 2 analysts, resulting in a savings of BRL 150K/year.
- TECH .NET, C#, React, Rabbit MQ, SQL Server, Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, Azure DevOps, AWS, TDD (Test-driven development), Razor.

Full Stack Software Developer

Oct 2020 - Jul 2021

Oliveira Trust

Developed scalable containerized APIs and queue consumers for managing investment fund operations.

- RESULT Enabled the decommissioning of modules from a legacy monolith and give a operational improvements to the analysts responsible to manage investment funds resulting in approximately 23% time savings for analyst, resulting in a savings of BRL 67,000/year.
- TECH PHP, Laravel, React, AWS, S3, SQS, SQL Server, MySQL, Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, GIT Lab, TDD (Test-driven development).

Full Stack Developer Nov 2016 – Oct 2020

Intercraft

Developed a voting module (API, Front-End) that was used in medical society elections.

• RESULT - This product eliminated the need for voters to travel to the headquarters and manually tally votes by 3 employees of the medical societies. Everything is now handled via the system in an easy and direct manner.

• TECH - Laravel, PHP, MySQL, React, IIS.

Developed a platform for registration, configuration, and provision of 360° virtual tours.

- RESULT Once it made virtual tours available, our real estate client saw an increase in website traffic and an improvement in visitor retention.
- TECH Laravel, PHP, MYSQL, Vue, IIS.

Developed a system for issuing and processing invoices for medical societies and condominiums.

- RESULT Automation to register invoices and process payments automatically replaced what previously required a team of 6 people at just one of the clients.
- TECH .NET, C#, React, PostgreSQL, Docker, GIT Hub, Windows Forms.

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced

Portuguese

Native